blumenthals.com 2016-03-14

# 1. Personally Identifiable Information:

                          Blumenthals.com PRIVACY POLICY
Blumenthals.com respects the privacy of every individual who visits our website(s). This
privacy statement provides notice of the standards and terms under which
Blumenthals.com protects the privacy of information supplied by visitors to sites on the
World Wide Web that are owned and operated by Blumenthals.com, including
Blumenthals.com.com. This privacy statement provides notice of our information
collection practices and of the ways in which your information may be used. This policy
may change from time to time, so please check back periodically to review this
information.
1. Personally Identifiable Information:
Blumenthals.com typically receives specific data about its website visitors only when
such information is provided voluntarily, such as when our visitors request information,
purchase or enroll for services, open a customer support inquiry ticket, provide resume
information for employment opportunities, or send us e-mail. Of course, some of these
activities require that you give us information, such as when you make a purchase, use a
credit card to pay for services, submit your resume, or request certain types of
information. When you provide personally identifiable information to Blumenthals.com
through one of our websites, it will be used to fulfill your specific request. In most
cases, you will be given the opportunity to select whether you do, or do not, want
Blumenthals.com to use this information for additional purposes. You may also request
that Blumenthals.com not use your information by sending an e-mail to
privacy@Blumenthals.com.com, however, Blumenthals.com reserves the right, in its
discretion, to send you bulletins and other important information about your
Blumenthals.com services. Absent any instructions from you, Blumenthals.com may use
information you provide to inform you about additional services and products offered by
the Blumenthals.com family of companies, Blumenthals.com venture companies,
Blumenthals.com authorized agents, and other goods and services providers with whom
Blumenthals.com has relationships and whose offerings might be of interest to you.
Blumenthals.com will not, however, sell or trade your personally identifiable information
unless we are authorized or legally required to do so, or in the case of imminent
physical harm to the visitor or others. On those Blumenthals.com sites where you may
provide Blumenthals.com with credit card or other ordering information via the web,
Blumenthals.com protects and secures this information by employing commercially
customary web-based security and encryption protocols, examples of which include
Secure Socket Layer (SSL) and Secure Electronic Transaction (SET). On those sites where
you voluntarily offer any feedback, data, answers, questions, comments, suggestions,
ideas or the like, Blumenthals.com will treat that portion of the information as non-
confidential and nonproprietary and, except as otherwise expressed in this privacy
statement, Blumenthals.com assumes no obligation to protect such information from
disclosure.
                                      www.blumenthals.com

 Page 2                                                                    July 20, 2011
2. Non Personally Identifiable (Generic) Information:
In general, Blumenthals.com gathers some generic information automatically. Generic
information does not reveal the identity of the visitor. It usually includes information
about the Internet address assigned to your computer, the number and frequency of
visitors, and the Blumenthals.com sites visited. Blumenthals.com gathers this
information for the limited purpose of determining customer service and website needs.
We accomplish this by using certain technologies, including "cookies" (a technology that
can be used to provide the visitor with tailored information about Blumenthals.com
services). Blumenthals.com does not combine information collected in this way with any
personally identifiable information. You can set your browser to notify you when you
receive a cookie and you can refuse it; this may however reduce functionality of certain
website features such as the order system and the Client Area.
3. Your Blumenthals.com hosted website, server, bulletin boards, forum,
Third-Party Sites:
Information that you disclose in a public space, including on any blog, bulletin board,
chat room, or website Blumenthals.com may host for you as part of your
Blumenthals.com services, is available to anyone else who visits that space.
Blumenthals.com cannot safeguard any information you disclose in these locations.
Additionally, Blumenthals.com websites contain links to sites that belong to third parties
unrelated to Blumenthals.com. Blumenthals.com cannot protect any information you
may disclose in these sites and recommends that you review the privacy policy
statements of those sites you visit.
4. Exceptions and Limitations:
Notwithstanding the foregoing and in compliance with applicable laws, Blumenthals.com
(i) cooperates fully with state, local, and federal officials in any investigation relating to
any content (including personal or private electronic communications transmitted to
Blumenthals.com) or purported unlawful activities of any user of the Service, and (ii)
takes reasonable measures to protect its proprietary rights. For the limited purposes of
accomplishing such cooperation and measures and in compliance with applicable laws,
Blumenthals.com may be required to disclose personally identifiable information. In
addition, Blumenthals.com may elect to monitor the areas of communication of any kind
(i) to satisfy any law, regulation, or government request; (ii) if such disclosure is
necessary or appropriate to operate Blumenthals.com; or (iii) to protect the rights or
property of Blumenthals.com or others. In connection with the potential sale or transfer
of any of its interest in Blumenthals.com.com, and other sites owned by the company,
Blumenthals.com reserves the right to sell or transfer your information (including, but
not limited to name, address information, and other information you provided to
Blumenthals.com) to a third party that (i) concentrates its business in communication
products or services; (ii) agrees to be Blumenthals.com's successor in interest with
regard to the maintenance and protection of information collected and maintained by
Blumenthals.com; and (iii) agrees to the obligations of this policy statement.
